<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Baking Recipe</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>


    <string name="aboutUs">
        This is one of the apps to let the Novice Baker to start their home and the Expert Baker can having more recipes to update themselves.
        \n\n
        Any Suggestion please email to:
        \n
        LoveBaking@gmail.com
        \n\n
        Data contributeAd by:
        \n
        www.LoveBaking.com.my
    </string>


    <!-- Bread -->
    <string name="chocolateChipBread">Chocolate Chip Banana Bread</string>
    <string name="chocolateChipBananaBread">

        Ingredients\n
        1/4 cup butter, softened\n
        1 cup sugar\n
        1 large egg, room temperature\n
        3 medium ripe bananas, mashed (about 1-1/4 cups)\n
        1 teaspoon vanilla extract\n
        2 cups all-purpose flour\n
        1 teaspoon baking soda\n
        1/2 teaspoon salt\n
        1 cup semisweet chocolate chips, divided\n
        \n
        Direction\n
        1. Preheat oven to 350°. In a large bowl, beat butter and sugar until crumbly. Beat in egg, bananas and vanilla. In another bowl, whisk flour, baking soda and salt; gradually beat into banana mixture. Stir in 1/2 cup chocolate chips.\n
        2. Transfer to a greased 10-in. cast-iron or other ovenproof skillet; sprinkle with remaining 1/2 cup chocolate chips. Bake until a toothpick inserted in center comes out clean, 25-30 minutes. Cool in pan on a wire rack.\n\n
        Nutrition Facts\n
        1 slice: 330 calories, 10g fat (6g saturated fat), 31mg cholesterol, 290mg sodium, 58g\n
        carbohydrate (34g sugars, 3g fiber), 4g protein.\n

    </string>


    <string name="garlicBread">Garlic Bread</string>
    <string name="garlicBreadContent">


        Ingredients\n
        1/2 cup butter, melted\n
        3 to 4 garlic cloves, minced\n
        1 loaf (1 pound) French bread, halved lengthwise\n
        2 tablespoons minced fresh parsley\n
        \n
        Directions\n
        1. In a small bowl, combine butter and garlic. Brush over cut sides of bread; sprinkle with parsley. Place, cut side up, on a baking sheet.\n
        2. Bake at 350° for 8 minutes. Broil 4-6 in. from the heat for 2 minutes or until golden brown. Cut into 2-in. slices. Serve warm.\n\n
        Nutrition Facts\n
        1 piece: 258 calories, 13g fat (7g saturated fat), 31mg cholesterol, 462mg sodium, 30g carbohydrate (1g sugars, 2g fiber), 5g protein.\n

    </string>


    <string name="irishSodaBread">Irish Soda Bread</string>
    <string name="irishSodaBreadContent">
    Ingredients\n
    3 cups all-purpose flour\n
    2/3 cup sugar\n
    3 teaspoons baking powder\n
    1 teaspoon salt\n
    1 teaspoon baking soda\n
    1 cup raisins\n
    2 large eggs, room temperature, beaten\n
    1-1/2 cups buttermilk\n
    1 tablespoon canola oil\n
        \n
    Directions\n
    1. Preheat oven to 350°. In a large bowl, combine first five ingredients. Stir in raisins. Set aside 1 tablespoon beaten egg. In a bowl, combine buttermilk, oil and remaining eggs; stir into flour mixture just until moistened (dough will be sticky). Transfer to a greased 9-in. round baking pan; brush top with reserved egg.\n\n
    2. Bake 45-50 minutes or until a toothpick inserted in the center comes out clean. Cool 10 minutes before removing from pan to a wire rack to cool. Cut into wedges.\n
    \nNutrition Facts\n
    1 wedge: 227 calories, 3g fat (1g saturated fat), 36mg cholesterol, 447mg sodium, 46g carbohydrate (20g sugars, 1g fiber), 6g protein.\n

    </string>


    <string name="cheesyGarlicBreadMeatballRing">Cheesy Garlic Bread Meatball Ring</string>
    <string name="cheesyGarlicBreadMeatballRingContent">

        Ingredients \n(For 8 servings)\n\n

        1 lb ground beef (455 g)\n
        1 egg\n
        ¼ cup bread crumbs (30 g)\n
        4 tablespoons Chopped fresh parsley, divided\n
        ½ tablespoon salt\n
        ½ tablespoon pepper\n
        1 batch pizza dough\n
        1 cup marinara sauce (260 g), plus more for serving\n
        1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese (100 g)\n
        ¼ cup butter, melted\n
        2 cloves garlic, minced\n
        2 tablespoons grated parmesan cheese\n
        \n
        Directions\n
        1. In a medium bowl, combine the ground beef, egg, bread crumbs, 2 tablespoons of parsley, salt, and pepper. Mix well.\n
        2. Pinch off a ball of the mixture, roll between your hands to make ping pong ball-sized meatball. Repeat with the rest of the meat.\n
        3. In a large pan, cook the meatballs over medium heat, turning to brown each side. Remove from heat and drain on a paper towel.\n
        4. Preheat oven to 350°F (180˚C).\n
        5. Pinch off a portion of pizza dough and, with your hands or a rolling pin, flatten out and top with a tablespoon of marinara sauce and mozzarella cheese. Add a meatball and wrap the dough over, pinching at the seams to close. Repeat with the remaining ingredients.\n
        6. Arrange the balls in a circle, seam-side down, in a large cast-iron skillet.\n
        7. Mix the melted butter with the garlic, remaining 2 tablespoons of parsley, and the Parmesan. Brush the balls with the garlic butter mixture.\n
        8. Bake for 20 minutes, or until golden brown. Let cool for 5-10 minutes.\n
        9. Place a bowl of warm marinara sauce in the middle of the skillet, then serve.\n

    </string>


    <string name="chickenParmesanStuffedGarlicBread">Chicken Parmesan-Stuffed Garlic Bread</string>
    <string name="chickenParmesanStuffedGarlicBreadContent">

        Ingredients\n
        (For 3 servings)\n\n

        1 boneless, skinless chicken breast\n
        2 cups flour (250 g)\n
        4 eggs, beaten\n
        2 cups seasoned breadcrumb (230 g)\n
        1 cup oil (240 mL), for frying\n
        1 large baguette\n
        10 slices mozzarella cheese\n
        marinara sauce\n\n
        GARLIC BUTTER\n

        ⅓ cup butter (75 g), melted\n
        3 cloves garlic, minced\n
        1 tablespoon fresh parsley, chopped\n
        1 tablespoon grated parmesan cheese\n\n

        Directions\n
        1. Slice the chicken breast into ½ inch (1 ¼ cm) thick strips.\n
        2. Place the flour, eggs, and bread crumbs into 3 separate bowls.\n
        3. Roll a chicken strip in the flour, dusting off excess. Dip the strip into the egg, then place into the bread crumbs, coating it completely.\n
        4. Repeat with the remaining chicken.\n
        5. Heat the oil in a pan over medium heat to 350˚F (180˚C).\n
        6. Preheat oven to 350°F (180˚C).\n
        7. Fry the breaded chicken strips until both sides are golden brown.\n
        8. Remove from heat and drain on a paper towel.\n
        9. Slice the baguette into thirds or fourths (each baguette piece should be roughly the same length of the fried chicken strips).\n
        10. Hollow out the insides of the baguette pieces with a knife.\n
        11. Lay two slices of mozzarella on top of each other with a 1 inch (2 ½ cm) overlap. Place a chicken strip on the overlapping region, then fold the mozzarella tightly around the chicken.\n
        12. Push the rolled chicken strips into a baguette piece.\n
        13. Slice the stuffed baguette pieces into 1 inch (2 ½ cm) slices, then place them tightly side-by-side on a baking sheet lined with foil.\n
        14. In a small bowl, mix together ingredients for garlic butter.\n
        15. Brush the garlic butter evenly over the baguette slices, making sure some drips in between the slices.\n
        16. Wrap the foil over the re-assembled baguette and bake for 20–25 minutes, until cheese is melted and the top is starting to brown.\n
        17. Remove the foil and serve with marinara!\n
        18. Nutrition Calories: 2689 Fat: 170 grams Carbs: 221 grams Fiber: 12 grams Sugars: 17 grams Protein: 67 grams\n

    </string>


    <!-- pie -->
    <string name="strawberryRhubarbPie">Strawberry Rhubarb Pie</string>
    <string name="strawberryRhubarbPieContent">
        
        Ingredients\n
        (For 6 servings)\n\n

        3 cups rhubarb (300 g), chopped\n
        3 cups strawberry (450 g), quartered\n
        1 cup sugar (200 g)\n
        ¼ cup cornstarch (30 g)\n
        ¼ teaspoon salt\n
        1 package pie dough\n
        whipped cream, to garnish\n\n

        Directions\n
        1. In a large bowl, toss the strawberries and rhubarb with the sugar, salt, and cornstarch. Set to the side.\n
        2. Line a pie tin with the pie dough.\n
        3. Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).\n
        4. Empty rhubarb and strawberry mixture into the pie tin, evenly distributing the mixture.\n
        5. Cut pie dough into strips and weave a lattice design on top of the pie. (You can also top with more pie dough in a full sheet with slits.)\n
        6. Bake the pie until the filling is bubbling and the crust is golden brown, about 2 hours. Cover the edge of the pie with foil if it begins to darken.\n
        7. Let cool slightly before serving.\n
        
    </string>


</resources>
